<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="article_survival">
		<text>Survival tips</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_survival_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_green]Survival tips%c[ui_gray_1]\n
			\nWelcome to the Chernobyl exclusion zone. This article will outline the basics of surviving in this hostile location.

            \n \n%c[pda_green]Food%c[ui_gray_1]
            \n• Some low tier mutant meat can be cooked directly over a lit campfire. This process is more time-consuming than cooking with proper equipment, but it can be a lifesaver.\n
            \nTo rust meat, just approach a lit campfire, open the inventory, and the option %c[pda_yellow]Roast%c[ui_gray_1] can be selected to cook the meat.\n

            \n• If you need charcoal to cook and have %c[pda_yellow]Wooden parts%c[ui_gray_1], just make a controlled burn to that wood into %c[pda_yellow]Field cooking kit%c[ui_gray_1], %c[pda_yellow]Army kettle%c[ui_gray_1] or %c[pda_yellow]Multi-fuel stove%c[ui_gray_1].\n

            \n \n%c[pda_green]Water%c[ui_gray_1]
            \nTo acquire potable water, you can get an %c[pda_yellow]Empty flask%c[ui_gray_1], stay over a water pool, and the option %c[pda_yellow]Fill%c[ui_gray_1] will be available. This way, you'll get a flask of %c[pda_yellow]Dirty water%c[ui_gray_1] that needs to be purified in the following ways:
            \n• Use an %c[pda_yellow]Akvatabs%c[ui_gray_1] on the Dirty water.
            \n• Boil the Dirty water on a lit campfire or in any cooking kit.

            \n \n%c[pda_green]Bleeding control%c[ui_gray_1]
            \nNo matter how well-equipped you are, blood loss can kill you really fast. For that reason, having some bandages is crucial to your survival. Bandages can be made by sterilizing fabric with some alcohol, combining both in inventory.\n
            \nYou can use %c[pda_yellow]Cloth sheets%c[ui_gray_1], %c[pda_yellow]Cloth sheets (synthetic)%c[ui_gray_1], %c[pda_yellow]Durable textiles%c[ui_gray_1] or %c[pda_yellow]Mil-spec textiles%c[ui_gray_1] as fabric.\n
            \nYou can use %c[pda_yellow]Nemiroff vodka%c[ui_gray_1], %c[pda_yellow]Putinka vodka%c[ui_gray_1] or %c[pda_yellow]Stolichnaya vodka%c[ui_gray_1] to sterilize the fabric.\n

            \n \n%c[pda_green]Campfire%c[ui_gray_1]
            \nAs you can see above, lit campfires are extremely useful. You can cook, purify water, and create a calming, safe area by litting a campfire out of the enemy's sight.\n
            \nTo lit a campfire, you can use a %c[pda_yellow]Matchbox%c[ui_gray_1], which can fail if the weather won't help, or you can use a %c[pda_yellow]Firestarter set%c[ui_gray_1], which can make lighting a campfire much easier in any weather condition.\n
            \nTo craft a %c[pda_yellow]Firestarter set%c[ui_gray_1], just combine a %c[pda_yellow]Wooden part%c[ui_gray_1] with a fuel.\n
            \nYou can use %c[pda_yellow]Matchbox%c[ui_gray_1], %c[pda_yellow]Kerosene%c[ui_gray_1] or %c[pda_yellow]Jerrycan%c[ui_gray_1] as fuel.\n
            \nIf you have both %c[pda_yellow]Firestarter set%c[ui_gray_1] and %c[pda_yellow]Matchbox%c[ui_gray_1] in your bag, you'll use the %c[pda_yellow]Firestarter set%c[ui_gray_1] if it's raining, else will use %c[pda_yellow]Matchbox%c[ui_gray_1].\n

            \n \n%c[pda_green]S.T.A.L.K.E.R. PDA Network%c[ui_gray_1]
            \nAlways monitor the %c[pda_yellow]Contacts%c[ui_gray_1] tab on your PDA. Even when it feels like you're alone in the area, your PDA can connect to nearby S.T.A.L.K.E.R.S. through the LoRa (Long Range) network. Advanced PDAs have an extended range, allowing them to transmit and receive signals over greater distances.\n
            
            \n \n%c[pda_green]Traveling through the Zone%c[ui_gray_1]
            \nReaching the heart of the Chernobyl Exclusion Zone requires extreme caution.\n
            \nTravel often means navigating forgotten and remote paths, sometimes hidden and lost to time. Only a handful of experienced stalkers know the Zone well enough or have the proper maps to move freely through it.\n
            \nOf course, once a specific route has been discovered, %c[pda_yellow]fast travel%c[ui_gray_1] becomes possible by simply following your PDA. Hiring a seasoned %c[pda_yellow]guide%c[ui_gray_1] can be expensive, but the time, resources, and dangers avoided along the way often make it a worthwhile investment.\n
		</text>
	</string>


</string_table>
