<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="article_combat">
		<text>How to survive in the zone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_combat_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_green]You are not a one-man army%c[ui_gray_1]\n
			\nTake care during combats to not be flanked by enemies, search for cover and %c[red]Don't Panic!%c[ui_gray_1] Even small calibers can easily kill you, then you need to stay calm to take the best action.\n
			
			\nBreaking enemies line of sight using smoke grenades to obfuscate the enemies vision or forcing them to run using explosive grenades can be a very effective strategy to make a combat scenario favorable to you.\n

			\nAgainst mutants, try to not be trigger-happy. Be a hunter and observe their movement pattern to get the best moment to attack.\n

			\n\n%c[pda_green]The armor system%c[ui_gray_1]\n
			\nArmors are not enough to protect you against bullets and mutants. To complete the protection, you'll need the extra protection from a %c[pda_yellow]Ballistic plate%c[ui_gray_1] equipped too. If you only wear the armor, it'll be servery damaged and the most part of the damage will bypass the protection.\n

			\nArmors with available belt slots can equip %c[pda_yellow]one ballistic plate%c[ui_gray_1] that will absorb much of the damage taken and will save the armor from being severely damaged and you from be severely injured.\n

			\nThere are many types of Ballistic plates in the zone, most of it are sold by mechanics, and there are rumors of powerful artifacts that can be used as indestructible ballistic plates.\n
            
            \n\n%c[pda_green]Mutants%c[ui_gray_1]\n
            \nEach mutant has a behavior and particularity. Hard skulls that mitigate headshots. Obsession to attack from behind, making him flee when spotted. Keep the gaze fixed on your weapon, giving you a chance to blind him with your hand flashlight. Attacking only in groups. Turning himself transparent or trying to control your mind are examples of those particularities.\n

            \nTry to identify the particularity of the mutant that you are fighting, and use the right tool/strategy to get the mutant down.\n

			\n\n%c[pda_green]Stealth%c[ui_gray_1]\n
			\nHumans are not omniscient; if they can't see you, they can't hurt you. Master the art of staying unseen to gain the upper hand in combat. Utilize silenced weapons to eliminate targets without drawing attention, and take advantage of the cover of night or the sound-muffling effects of rain to move undetected.\n

			\nMutants, on the other hand, rely heavily on their other senses. Armor camouflage may be less effective when facing these creatures.\n

			\nSome armor is more effective than others for blending into your surroundings. Choose your gear wisely to match your stealth tactics. Camouflage patterns and darker shades can help you remain unnoticed in various environments, from dense forests to urban ruins. Remember, the right armor not only protects you but also enhances your ability to stay hidden.\n
		</text>
	</string>


</string_table>
